That
[music] I have been
listening to it since childhood Who has seen tomorrow
Today I am feeling it for the first time
I had thought that I will have to think twice before leaving the house
[applause]
Forget hugging, even shaking hands will be difficult There is no
problem in learning
Welcoming guests in the body will be such
that
knowledge and science will be amazed The
faces of superheroes will change
I had thought that
Who would have thought that rockstars will emerge there
Grandparents, there is internet and people will drown
in cooking We will click on the pictures of our loved ones that we will make
so much of our life that we will
see it not tomorrow but from today
While it is precious, we do not take any chances Do it, do it, that is why
ICICI Prudential Life's
iProtect All in One Temple Run We will see tomorrow or today